Woody Allen Papers, 1955-2012: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 3: Additions, 1999; 5.0 boxes
  - Scripts, 1995-1998; 5.0 boxes
    - Celebrity, 1997-1998; 2.0 boxes
      - Woody Allen's working copy, circa 1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
      - Original version produced by Studio Duplicating, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      - Marked version by Woody Allen, circa 1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      - Revised script, 1997 February 12; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
      - Selected revisions, 1997 April 7; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
      - Revised script & showing schedule, 1997 June 9; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
      - Revised script, 1997 July 3; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
      - Revised script, 1997 August 6; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
      - Two copies of the script, undated; 2.0 folders (Folder 2-3)
    - "Central Park West", 1995; more than 2 folders
      - "A One Act Play" (7 copies), undated; 7.0 folders (Folder 1-7)
      - "A Play in Two Acts", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
    - Deconstructing Harry, 1997; 2.0 boxes
      - Woody Allen's working copy, circa 1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
      - Woody Allen's second marked version, circa 1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      - Final version, circa 1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      - Author's edited copy, circa 1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
      - Marked xerox copy, circa 1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
      - Author's marked script, circa 1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
      - Author's marked script, circa 1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      - Four copies of the script, undated; 4.0 folders (Folder 3-6)
- Series 4: Additions, 2000; 2.0 folders
  Consists of manuscripts for Sweet and Lowdown.
  - Sweet and Lowdown, 1998; 2.0 folders
    - Original script, AMs & TMs, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
    - Photocopy, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
- Series 5: Additions, 1955-2008; 16.0 boxes
  Additions made in 2007.
  This series is arranged into three subseries: Writings: Manuscripts, Screenplays and Essays, Correspondence, Copyrights, Agreements, etc, and Printed Material.
  - Subseries 5A: Writings: Manuscripts, Screenplays and Essays, 1955-2008; 14.0 boxes
    This subseries contains original manuscripts, typescripts, and copies of manuscripts of Allen's books, screenplays and prose pieces written for different magazines and journals. Some of the manuscripts have not been published or produced as films. The manuscripts include drafts for Allen's more recent movie projects, Cassandra's Dream (2007) and Midnight in Barcelona (released as Vicky Cristina Barcelona, 2008). The folders are arranged in alphabetical order by title or by subject. There are two boxes of miscellaneous, untitled manuscripts, screenplays and essays at the end.
    - "Above the Law, Below the Box Springs", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
      2 TMss with autograph corrections, 6 pp. and 5 pp. Originally published as a "casual" piece in the Nov. 21, 2005 issue of The New Yorker.
    - "Anything Else" (unpublished novel), undated; more than 4 folders (Folder 2-5)
      This was Allen's first attempt at writing a novel (only time to date). It was never given out for publication and eventually turned into a film script.
      - Version 1, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 355 pp. "First earliest" written in pencil on title page.
      - Version 2, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 355 pp.
      - Version 3, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 291 pp.
    - Anything Else (2003 film): Screenplay, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 84 pp.
    - "The Average Housewife", circa 1955; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      TMs with one autograph correction, 3 pp. Early attempt at short story writing (unpublished)
    - Bananas (1971 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs of screenplay, 89 pp.
    - "A Brief Explanation" / "But Soft...Real Soft", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      TMs, 4 pp.; TMs with a different title ("But Soft...Real Soft"); Xerox copy with autograph corrections.
    - "A Brief Guide to Civil Disobedience", 1972; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      3 TMss, 1 with autograph corrections and 1 Xerox copy of autograph corrections. Published as "A Brief, Yet Helpful, Guide to Civil Disobedience" in the July 15, 1972 edition of The New York Times.
    - "By Destiny Denied", 1976-1979; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
      2 TMss with autograph corrections, 7 and 9 pp, and a TL from The New Yorker's Fiction Department; original tear sheets from the Feb. 22, 1976 issue of The New Yorker. This piece was also published under the title "Incident at Entwhistle's."
    - Cassandra's Dream (film), 2007; 4.0 boxes
      - Original version, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
        TMs (pp. 1-2) and AMs (pp. 3-63) with autograph corrections
      - Middle draft, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 84 pp.
      - Later version, 2006 April 20; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 121 pp.
    - "Caution: Falling Moguls", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
      AMs with autograph corrections, 7 pp.; TMss (original and Xerox) with autograph corrections, 7 pp. This was published as "casual" piece in The New Yorker(date unknown).
    - "Central Park West" (one-act play), 1999 March 19; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
      TMs, 60 pp., and Xerox copy
    - "The Chair", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
      4 Xerox copies: 2 TMss, 9 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 6 pp.; AMs with autograph corrections, 8 pp.
    - "The Condemned", 1977-1980; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
      The New Yorker's TMs copy with their suggested changes, 9 pp., TMs, associated business correspondence and documents; original tear sheets from the Nov. 21, 1977 issue of The New Yorker. Originally titled "The Chair."
    - "Confessions of a Burglar", 1976 October 18; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
      The New Yorker's TMss (original and Xerox copies) with their suggested changes, 9 pp.; original tear sheets from the Oct. 18, 1976 issue of The New Yorker.
    - "Controversial Era", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
      Original TMs, 4 pp., of unpublished television or theatrical sketch typed by Allen and 2 carbon copies
    - "Cupid's Shaft", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
      4 TMs and 3 Xerox copies of short story ( total), many with autograph corrections; 2 early versions are titled "What Happens to Certain Incurable/Incorrigible Romantics." Includes notes about making script anglicized for London shoot.
    - The Curse of the Jade Scorpion (2001 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      AMs of screenplay with autograph corrections written on a yellow legal notepad.
    - Deconstructing Harry (1997 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      TMs (bound), 132 pp.
    - "Desperate Circumstances", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 5 pp.
    - "The Diet", 1979-1983; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      The New Yorker's TMs copy with their suggested changes/autograph corrections (2nd version submitted on 12/5/79), 8 pp.; TMs (original version); TL from The New Yorker's Fiction Department; 2 TMss (copies, including miscellaneous pages) typed by Allen with his autograph corrections; original tear sheets from the Feb. 25, 1980 issue of The New Yorker.
    - "Doctor Schweitzer", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      TMs, 5 pp.
    - "The Early Essays", 1973-1976; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
      TMs, 7 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 7 pp.; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 3 pp.; TL from The New Yorker's Fiction Department; original tear sheets from the January 20, 1973 issue of The New Yorker.
    - Everything You've Always Wanted to Know About Sex... (film), 1972; 1.0 item
      - Version 1, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
        TMs with autograph corrections, approximately 270 pp.
      - Version 2, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
        TMs (bound with green cover) and includes ANS by Allen to "Jack" on title page.
      - Version 3, 1971 August 20; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
        TMs (carbon copy), 18 pp.; TMss, 17 pp; TMs (Xerox), 7 pp.
      - Miscellaneous, 1972; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
        AMs, 4 pp.; TMs (carbon) of Captions for Everything You Always Wanted To Know About Sex..., 3 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Q & A) by Allen, 1 p.; TLS by the Managing Editor of Playboy to Allen.
    - "Examining Psychic Phenomena", 1972-1975; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
      TMss (original and Xerox), 10 pp.; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 12 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 6 pp. Includes original tear sheets from the October 7, 1972 issue of The New Yorker.
    - "Excerpts from My Speech to the Graduating Class", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
      3 Xerox copies: AMs (6 pp.) and TMs (3 pp.) with autograph corrections, and TMs, 6 pp. (published in the New York Times, date unknown)
    - "Fabrizio's: Criticism and Response", 1979-1982; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
      The New Yorker's TMs copy with their suggested changes, 10 pp., and TL from the Fiction Department; original tear sheet from the February 5, 1979 issue of The New Yorker; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 7 pp.; TMs (Xerox), 9 pp., and TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 7 pp., both titled "The Life of the Mind."
    - "Fabulous Tales and Mythical Beasts", 1974; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
      AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 8 pp.; TMs, 6 pp.; TL (carbon) from Allen's assistant to The New Republic; original tear sheets from the November 30, 1974 issue of The New Republic.
    - "A Fan's Notes on Earl Monroe", 1990; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
      AMs with autograph corrections, 13 pp.; photocopy and facsimile copy of the published article in Sport magazine.
    - "Feet of Clay - Big Shoes", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
      TMs with autograph notes at the bottom of the first page, 4 pp.
    - "Feldman's Hostility", 1978 November; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
      TMss (original and Xerox), 11 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 11 pp.
    - "Fine Times: An Oral Memoir", 1975-1978; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
      TMs, 5 pp.; original tear sheets from the March 17, 1975 issue of The New Yorker and a Xerox copy; TL from their Fiction Department.
    - "Five Dollars for the Bright Sayings of Children", circa 1955; 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      TMs, 1 p. (example of one of Allen's very early comic bits)
    - Getting Even (book), 1971; more than 19 folders (Folder 1-18)
      TMss with autograph corrections of Contents list, 1 p., and summary draft, 1 p., for the book, a collection of comic essays.
      - Contents list and summary, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
        TMss with autograph corrections, 2 pp.
      - "The Metterling Lists", 1969; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
        AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 9 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 8 pp.; original tear sheets from the May 10, 1969 issue of The New Yorker
      - "A Look at Organized Crime", 1970; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
        The New Yorker's TMs (working proof) copy with their autograph corrections, 10 pp.; original tear sheets from the August 15, 1970 issue of The New Yorker; TMs pages, some with autograph corrections.
      - "The Schmeed Memoirs", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs, 7 pp.
      - "My Philosophy", 1969-1972; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
        TMss with autograph corrections, 5 and 7 pp., and some photocopies; tear sheets (Xerox) from the December 27, 1969 issue of The New Yorker.
      - "Yes, But Can the Steam Engine Do This?", 1966; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
        TMs, 7 pp.; original tear sheets from the October 8, 1966 issue of The New Yorker and the Literary Calvacade.
      - "Death Knocks", 1968-1997; 1.0 folder (Folder 7)
        TMs (facsimile) with autograph corrections, 15 pp.; tear sheets and reprints from the July 27, 1968 issue of The New Yorker; 1997 TL request re. a proposed chamber opera.
      - "Spring Bulletin", 1967; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
        TMss, 5 pp. (original and carbon); original tear sheets from the April 29, 1967 issue of The New Yorker.
      - "Hassidic Tales, With a Guide to Their Interpretation by the Noted Scholar", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
        TMs, 8 pp.; TMs and AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox); original tear sheet from an undated issue of The New Yorker.
      - "The Gossage-Vardebedian Papers", 1966; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 11 pp. (includes carbon copies); original tear sheets from the January 22, 1966 issue of The New Yorker.
      - "Notes from the Overfed", 1968; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
        TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), pp. 2-6; tear sheets (Xerox) from the March 16, 1968 issue of the The New Yorker.
      - "A Twenties Memory", 1963; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
        TMs, 6 pp.; Chicago Daily News (incomplete Xerox), 1 p.
      - "Count Dracula", 1971-1995; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
        TMs rewrite for Random House dated 4/1/71, 7 pp. (original and Xerox copies); 1995 TL reprint request for inclusion in a book titled Vampires, Wine and Roses.
      - "A Little Louder, Please", 1966; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 1 p.; TMs and AMs draft pages (Xerox); original tear sheets from the May 28, 1966 issue of The New Yorker.
      - "Conversations with Helmholtz", 1971; 1.0 folder (Folder 15)
        TMs rewrite, 8 pp., for Random House dated 4/1/71 (multiple copies); AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox).
      - "Viva Vargas!", 1969-1971; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 8 pp. (several copies); original tear sheets from the August 1969 issue (#69) of Evergreen Review; AMs, 7 pp., and TMs, 2 pp., both with autograph corrections (Xerox); TMs rewrite, 9 pp., for Random House dated 4/1/71.
      - "The Discovery and Use of the Fake Ink Blot", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
        TMss, 3 pp. (original, Xerox, carbon) and tear sheet (facsimile) from the August 1966 issue of Playboy.
      - "Mr. Big", 1996; 1.0 folder (Folder 18)
        TMs, 13 pp. (original and facsimile) and TL dated 1996
    - "A Giant Step for Mankind", 1980; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
      Essay for the June 9, 1980 issue of The New Yorker (includes tear sheets).
    - "Glitz To Stockholm", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 20)
      AMs, 2 pp.
    - "Glory, Hallelujah, Sold!", 2005 September 7; 1.0 folder (Folder 21)
      Original AMs and Allen's TMs copy, both with autograph corrections
    - "Going, Going, Gone", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 22)
    - "Gregor", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 23)
      Unpublished TMs, 9 pp. (original and xerox)
    - "A Guide to Some of the Lesser Ballets", 1972; 1.0 folder (Folder 24)
      TMs and TMs with autograph corrections, 10 pp.; TMs and AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox); original tear sheets from the October 28, 1972 issue of The New Yorker.
    - "The Gun", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 25)
      Unpublished TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 15 pp.
    - "The Happy Couple", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
      Unpublished TMs (Xerox), 9 pp.
    - "Hard Times, Come No More", circa 1955; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
      TMs, 3 pp. (comic piece made into a stand-up routine)
    - "The Heavy", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      TMS, 6 pp.; miscellaneous AMs and TMs pages with autograph corrections (Xerox), 9 pp.
    - "Heaven Knows, Anything Goes", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
      AMs with autograph corrections, 7 pp.; 2 TMss with autograph corrections, 5 and 7 pp.
    - "The Hi-Fi Driver", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 5)
      TMs and TMs (carbon) of a theatrical sketch, 4 pp. each
    - "The Holdup", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
      TMs of a theatrical sketch, 3 pp.
    - Hollywood Ending (2002 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 93 pp.
    - "Hollywood Wedding", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 6 pp.
    - "A House is Definitely Not a Home", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 9)
      TMs, 9 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 9 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 10 pp.; 2 TMss (original and carbon), 12 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 5 pp. Unpublished casual.
    - "How I Blew A Million Dollars in My Full Time", 1964; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
      TMs, 3 pp., TMs with autograph corrections, 4 pp.; TLS rejection letter from TV Guide to Charles Joffe dated May 19, 1964
    - "If The Impressionists Were Dentists", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 11)
      TMs, 6 pp.; TMss (original and Xerox) with autograph corrections, 5 pp.
    - "Incident at Entwhistle's", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
      TMs (Xerox), 7 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 5 pp.; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 7 pp. This was alternatively titled "By Destiny Denied."
    - "Interview with a Star", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 13)
      TMs, 2 pp.
    - "The Irish Genius", 1974-1977; 1.0 folder (Folder 14)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 7 pp. (revised 8/74); 2 TMss (Xerox, revised 2/4/75); TMs (Xerox) of proof with autograph corrections, 4 pp.; original tear sheets from the Feb. 22, 1975 issue of The New Republic; AMs and TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox).
    - "It Beats Waiting on Tables -- I Guess", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 15)
    - "The Kugelmass Episode", 1977-1980; 1.0 folder (Folder 16)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 20 pp.; TMs, 18 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 12 pp.; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 17 pp.; original tear sheets from the May 2, 1977 issue of The New Yorker. This story won the 1978 O. Henry award.
    - "Loveborg's Women Considered", 1974-1977; 1.0 folder (Folder 17)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 6 pp.; original tear sheets from the October 28, 1974 issue of The New Yorker; TL from their Fiction Department.
    - Love and Death (1975 film), 1.0 item (Folder 18)
      TMs, 113 pp.
    - "The Lunatic's Tale", 1977; 1.0 folder (Folder 19)
      TMss (Xerox), 10 pp., published in the 4/77 issue of The New Republic; TMss with autograph corrections (Xerox), 6 and 10 pp.; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 9 pp.
    - Match Point (film), 2005; more than 5 folders (Folder 1-4)
      - Screenplay draft, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
        Original TMs version on yellow paper with autograph corrections, approximately 77 pp., as typed by Woody Allen. "Untitled" written on the cover page.
      - Screenplay draft, 2004 April 12; 1.0 item (Folder 2)
        TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 260 pp. (pages out of order)
      - Screenplay draft, 2004 April 12; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 260 pp.
      - Screenplay draft, 2004 May 3; 1.0 folder (Folder 4)
        Includes photocopies of an e-mail titled "Names" (4/29/04) and a printed document titled "Notes on WASP 2004 / L.D 28th April 2004."
    - "Match Wits with Inspector Ford", 1972 December; 1.0 folder (Folder 1)
      3 TMss, 8 pp. (original, Xerox and Xerox with autograph corrections); TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 10 pp.; uncorected proofs, 2 pp.; original tear sheets from Playboy.
    - "Mayor's Monologue" (Lindsay), undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      TMs (carbon), 5 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 2 pp.; TMs, 1 p.
    - Melinda and Melinda (2004 film), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 3)
      TMs (Xerox) with autograph corrections, 76 pp.
    - Mere Anarchy (2007 book): Proofs, 2006; 1.0 folder
      - "To Err is Human -- To Float, Divine", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs (Xerox) with autograph corrections, 9 pp.
      - "Tandoori Ransom", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 7 pp.
      - "Sam, You Made the Pants Too Fragrant", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "This Nib For Hire", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 8 pp.
      - "Calisthenics, Poison Ivy, Final Cut", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 9 pp.
      - "How Deadly Your Tastebuds My Sweet", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "Glory Hallelujah, Sold!", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
      - "Caution: Falling Moguls", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs (Xerox of final draft), 10 pp.; TMs (Xerox) with autograph corrections, 10 pp.
      - "The Rejection", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs, 4 pp.
      - "Pinchuk's Law", 2006; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        TMs, 5 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 4 pp.; galley proof with autograph corrections for The New Yorker (Xerox), 5 pp.
    - Mere Anarchy (2007 book): Publisher's proofs, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
      TMs of publisher's proofs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 106 pp. Remaining pieces (not already listed above) are: "Sing, You Sacher Torts"; "On a Bad Day You Can See Foreve"; "Attention Geniuses: Cash Only"; "Strung Out"; "Above the Law, Below the Box Springs"; "Thus Ate Zarathustra"; "Surprise Rocks the Disney Trial."
    - Midnight in Barcelona (film), 2008; more than 3 folders (Folder 6-7)
      The film was released under the title of Vicky Cristina Barcelona.
      - First, handwritten draft, 2007 January; 1.0 item (Folder 6)
        AMs, 58 pp.
      - Typed version, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
        TMs, 81 pp.
    - "Midnight in Barcelona" film script made into Parisian movie script(?), undated; 1.0 item (Folder 8)
      AMs, 65 pp.
    - "Monopoly", 1958; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      4 TMss (1 with autograph corrections), 5 pp.
    - "My Apology", 1978; 1.0 item (Folder 10)
      TMss (original and Xerox), 8 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (xerox), 5 pp.
    - "My Ten Best", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
      2 TMss (xerox), 5 pp.
    - "My War with the Machines", 1965-1971; 1.0 folder (Folder 12)
      TLS dated 1971 (Xerox) and original tear sheets from Playboy.
    - "Nanny Dearest", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 1)
    - Natividad Abascal, undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 2)
      TMs (original and Xerox), 1 p. text for Playboy magazine spread for the female character named "Natividad Abascal" in the Bananas film.
    - "Nefarious Times We Live In", 1975; 1.0 folder (Folder 3)
      TMs, 6 pp.; AMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 3 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections (Xerox), 4 pp.; original tear sheet from the Nov. 22, 1975 issue of The New Republic.
    - "New Milford" (one-act play), 2000-2003; 1.0 item (Folder 4-7)
      Earlier title was "New London"
      - Version 1, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 4)
        AMs, 15 pp.
      - Version 2, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 5)
        TMs with autograph corrections, 31 pp. Handwritten on cover page: "Writer's Block - Two One Act Plays - Woody Allen 1) New York, 2) New Milford."
      - Versions 3-5, 2000-2002; 1.0 folder (Folder 6)
        TMs (July 26, 2000-Jan. 24, 2001), 33. pp.; (Sept. 12, 2002), 33 pp.; (Oct. 21, 2002), 34 pp.
      - Version 6, 2003; 1.0 item (Folder 7)
        TMs (May 24, 2003), 34 pp.
    - "No Kaddish for Weinstein", 1975-1978; 1.0 folder (Folder 8)
      TMs, 6 pp.; The New Yorker's TMs copy with their autograph corrections, 6 pp., and a TL from their Fiction Dept.; original tear sheets from the March 3, 1975 issue of The New Yorker.
    - Notes for Record Album, undated; 1.0 item (Folder 9)
      TMs with autograph corrections, 1 p., and 1 p. of handwritten "Editing instructions" for Volumes 1-3.
    - "Opening Night", undated; 1.0 folder (Folder 10)
      TMs (carbon), 7 pp., and TMs (Xerox), 6 pp., of a sketch (first thing ever produced on stage by author).
    - "Park Avenue, High Floor, Must Sell - Or Jump", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 11)
    - "Passion Play", undated; 1.0 item (Folder 12)
      AMs with autograph corrections, 7 pp.
    - "The Penalty", 1990; 1.0 folder (Folder 13)
      TMs (Xerox), 5 pp.; TMs with autograph corrections, 5 pp.; TLS (Xerox) by Allen to Roger Rosenblatt.